Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
This world is a riot of color
Truth and lies fool our eyes
Look carefully with your heart
Find the truth in the ancestral courtyard
Hey you, good or bad, truth or lies
Can't escape the gray smoke in your heart
Bring all your courage
Maybe you can save this world
Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
In the last episode, Jingjing, the angel above the clouds
fell to the human world because of a failed spell
And the forgetful student Locky, by a lucky chance
became Jingjing's savior
The truant boy
Locky
You're the king of being late!
I'm not late today!
There are thirty-one days in a month
You were on time only one day
Tell me, what have you got to be proud of?
What are you laughing at?
Is it that funny?
Come in.
This is our new classmate, Jingjing.
She just transferred here from another town.
From now on, everyone should take good care of her.
Hello everyone.
Jingjing.
Please take your seat and get ready for class.
Okay.
We'll have a pop quiz now.
What's that "huh" for?
You must learn and practice.
Absolutely no.
Slacking off.
Jingjing.
If you can't do it, that's okay.
I'll give you extra lessons.
Thank you, teacher.
Jingjing's not scared.
No talking.
No looking around.
Okay.
Knowledge Elf.
I need your help.
Leave it to me.
Time's up.
Hand in your papers.
Exam's over?
Today's lesson is dissecting a goldfish.
No looking around.
Begin dissecting.
Poor thing...
Now the little goldfish can go back to living in the water.
No talking.
No looking around.
Locky!
You actually put the goldfish back in the tank?
Are you trying to wreck my lesson plan?
Why is it always you causing trouble in class?
You're done for today.
Come with me to the office.
Locky.
You've been getting more and more out of line lately.
Not only do you show up late...
Now you're disrupting class again.
About this morning's exam—
I haven't even gotten to you yet.
And now you're at it again.
It's not like it's my first time failing.
What are you muttering about?
You cheated, and you still think you're right?
I didn't cheat.
Then explain this.
All correct!
From the day you started school,
when have you ever passed an exam?
I don't know what happened.
I fell asleep during the exam.
I didn't cheat.
Looks like you've not only learned to cheat,
but also learned to lie.
Late to school,
cheating on exams,
disrupting class,
and lying on top of that.
I've never seen such a terrible kid as you.
Have your parents come to school tomorrow.
Locky!
Class missile!
Late and cheating!
No shame!
Locky, look!
This gem is so beautiful!
Who exactly are you?
What's with that fish tank?
What exactly are you following me for?
I'm an angel!
Locky saved me.
I'm here to repay him!
Curly, don't give me that!
I really am an angel.
Remember the black rabbit that scared you off this morning?
I'll make it appear again so you can see.
Okay!
Little black rabbit, little black rabbit!
Curly, stop messing around.
Hurry home and do your homework.
I really am an angel.
Maybe I've been away from the sky too long,
so my powers have grown weak.
I'm the one who filled in your exam paper for you!
So it was you! Why are you trying to ruin me?
Because I'm an angel repaying a kindness!
Jingjing could tell at a glance that Locky is a dimwit,
bad at studying,
a kid hated by teachers and classmates.
So I wanted to help you get good grades,
so everyone would like you!
Angel repaying a kindness? Teachers and classmates?
Anyway, I'm just a dim-witted, bad-at-studying, always-late, good-for-nothing guy.
You all hate me.
I hate you all too.
Don't any of you boss me around!
I'm never going to school again!
Little girl, who are you?
I'm Jingjing.
I'm here to find Locky.
You're his classmate, right?
First time a classmate's come to see Locky.
Doesn't Locky have any friends?
Yeah, that kid's got a bad temper.
Very few people are willing to play with him.
Oh, I forgot to introduce myself.
I'm Locky's uncle, Jimmy Chen.
Come in.
Hello, Uncle.
That kid's probably upstairs.
I'll go get him down.
Stay here tonight.
And have dinner with us.
Locky!
Your friend came to play with you!
You...
Sleeping so early?
Afraid you'll be late tomorrow?
He's really asleep.
Uncle...
Everyone hates me.
I don't want to go to school anymore.
Locky...
A real man facing problems
should never back down.
But I really don't want to go to school.
Then what do you want to do?
I want to be like you, Uncle—
a mighty and impressive
great detective!
No, no.
A cartoon hero skipping school would be a bad influence on the kids!
I don't care! I don't care! I don't care!
I just want to be a detective!
I'm never going back to school!
Why don't we go eat first?
No! No! No! No!
If you won't let me be a detective,
then I won't eat!
Uncle,
you said I could be a detective—so keep your word!
But your studies really can't be delayed.
Just so happens, I'm free tomorrow.
I can go talk to the teacher first.
No, the teacher doesn't believe me at all.
I don't want to go to school.
I want to be a detective with Uncle!
I hate annoying problems like "A plus B, all squared."
Hello? It's me.
Locky, there's an urgent case. I have to go.
Uncle, I'm going too.
No.
Uncle, you're cheating.
You promised I could be a detective.
Sorry, Locky.
It's urgent. I have to go.
Uncle, you big liar!
The rare treasure Angel's Tear will be exhibited at the city museum.
A rare opportunity.
Locky, let's go to the museum to see Angel's Tear together.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Curly, go home now.
Stop bothering me.
[Ending Theme]
Every day is just sunrise and sunset.
Step into a world and dream more
Long for every second, every moment of life
My bright eyes sparkle
A smile that greets the sun
Soft steps at the crossing by Qian'an's home